CHAD LISCINSKY

San Francisco, California | 415 505 5859 | chadliscinsky@gmail.com | LinkedIn

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Account Management, Sales and Customer Success Professional with a proven record of positive results in executing strategic plans to meet company objectives. Highly experienced creating essential partnerships and lasting relationships with current and prospective clients. Technology focused, problem solver and here to make the workplace an exciting and inspiring environment to thrive in. My passion for growth, success and new technology combined with my creative drive keeps customers engaged while bringing their visions to life.

WORK EXPERIENCE

DIRECTOR OF SALES | ENCORE EVENT TECHNOLOGIES, SAN FRANCISCO, CA

June 2017 - Present

- Develop and execute a highly successful engagement strategy that proactively maintains high customer satisfaction leading to a consistent customer capture and return rate of 94%+
- Lead and mentor a skilled team of Account Executives generating a 17%+ Increase in overall revenues year over year
- Successfully maintained business for over 30 Enterprise level accounts while focusing on building new lasting relationships
- Integrate technical expertise of product with industry best practices for all customers leading to the positive execution of large complex events
- Interface with Senior Leadership to help strategize and create beneficial customer facing marketing materials for all partners
- Maintain and enhance customer satisfaction by providing ongoing, proactive support throughout the customer life cycle

SENIOR ACCOUNT EXECUTIVE | PSAV, SAN FRANCISCO, CA

June 2014 – May 2017

- Managed the Enterprise tech, corporate and association business utilizing a 360 degree sales approach ensuring return business across the globe
- Consistently top 3rd or above revenue generating Account Manager in the west super region
- Worked directly with clients and producers to develop and provide them with new concepts for their events including CAD development and production schedule securing flawless events
- Reported directly to the PSAV Director of Sales with consistent revenue forecasts and updates

INSIDE SALES ASSOCIATE | TICKETFLY SAN FRANCISCO, CA

March 2012 - June 2014

- Prospected leads within specific verticals to provide the senior sales team with qualified appointments
- Responsible for all sales activities, from lead generation to signed agreements
- Developed and maintained a complete database of leads and clients within Salesforce CRM
- Demonstrated product knowledge to allow for effective presentation of Ticketfly's software and services leading to an overall increase in demand for the platform
- Maintained accurate records of all sales and prospecting activities including sales calls, demonstrations, closed sales and follow up activities

ACCOUNT EXECUTIVE | SWANK AUDIO VISUALS, SAN FRANCISCO, CA

May 2007 - March 2012

- Coordinated over 500+ events with a consistent 10%+ YOY increase in overall revenues
- Worked directly with Technical Directors for initial event conception
- Managed client's budgets for all audio visual and IT needs necessary for their events
- Achieved sales targets on a consistent basis

SKILL HIGHLIGHTS

Customer SuccessJIRAAccount ManagementRelationship BuildingHTML 5Business DevelopmentLeadershipCSS 3Customer ExperienceProblem SolvingSalesforce CRMResults

EDUCATION

New England Institute of Art Bachelor of Arts, Audio Production

ACTIVITIES

Music, Film, Travel, Production, Audio, Computer Technology, Outdoors and Food